http://www.nesea.org/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
ConferencesBuildingEnergy BostonRequest for ProposalsMeet the Content CommitteeBuildingEnergy NYCPast ConferencesBuildingEnergy NYC 2020About BuildingEnergy NYCPricingSchedule At A GlanceSessionsMethods & Materials ShowcaseCommunity EventsSpeakersEvaluationsSponsors & ExhibitorsCEUsMedia KitMeet the Content CommitteeWho's AttendingRequest for ProposalsBuildingEnergy Boston 2020About BuildingEnergy BostonSchedule At A GlancePricingVirtual TourSessionsSpeakersTrade ShowPre-Conference WebinarsCEUsNESEA NightWho's AttendingMeet the Content CommitteeMedia KitFAQsAttendees FAQsSpeaker FAQsExhibitor FAQsCOVID-19 UpdatesSponsor InformationBuildingEnergy NYC 2019About BuildingEnergy NYCSchedule At A GlanceSessionsSpeakersTrade ShowOpening ReceptionMeet the Content CommitteeRequest for ProposalsCEUsMedia KitFAQsAttendee FAQsExhibitor FAQsSpeaker FAQsBuildingEnergy Boston 2019About BuildingEnergy BostonSchedule At A GlanceSessionsSpeakersTrade ShowSponsorsMeet the Content CommitteeNESEA NightCEUsMedia KitTravel & AccommodationsConference ProgramFAQsAttendees FAQsSpeaker FAQsExhibitor FAQsBuildingEnergy NYC 2018About BuildingEnergy NYCSchedule At A GlancePre-Conference WorkshopsConference SessionsSpeakersTrade ShowSponsorsNESEA Annual MeetingFAQsAttendee FAQsExhibitor FAQsMeet the Content CommitteeMedia Kit2017 Recorded SessionsRequest for ProposalsCEUsBuildingEnergy Boston 2018About BuildingEnergy BostonSchedule At A GlanceShow ProgramSpeakersSessionsAll SessionsThursday 10:30amThursday 1:30pmThursday 3:30pmFriday 9:00amFriday 10:30amFriday 1:30pmFriday 3:00pmSponsorsTrade ShowNESEA NightTravel & AccommodationPlanning CommitteeFAQsAttendee FAQsSpeaker FAQsExhibitor FAQsMedia KitCEUsEmerging Professionals Career ForumBuildingEnergy NYC 2017About BuildingEnergy NYCSchedule At A GlanceSession GridSessionsAll Sessions9:30 Sessions11:30 Sessions1:30 Sessions3:30 SessionsSpeakersTrade ShowSponsorsMeet the Planning CommitteeFAQsAttendee FAQsSpeaker FAQsExhibitor FAQsTravel & AccommodationsMedia KitEmerging Professionals Career Forum: NYCBuildingEnergy Boston 2017At A GlancePre-Conference WorkshopsConference SessionsTrade ShowCommunity EventsMeet the Conference ChairsSpeakersSponsorsMedia KitGuidebookFAQsAttendee FAQsExhibitor FAQsSpeaker FAQsCEUsBuildingEnergy NYC 2016PricingSchedule GridConference SessionsSession PresentationsSpeakersTrade ShowSponsorsMedia KitHotel AccomodationsVolunteerGuidebookBuildingEnergy Bottom Lines Business Summit 2016BuildingEnergy 2016AboutPricingAt A GlanceScheduleSession PresentationsSpeakersSponsorsExhibitorsInformation about ExhibitingExhibitor FAQsTravel & AccommodationsCEUsConference GuidebookBuildingEnergy Bottom Lines Business Summit 2015BuildingEnergy NYC 2015AboutPricingScheduleSpeakersSponsorsExhibitorsTravel & AccommodationsContinuing EducationSponsor BuildingEnergy NYCExhibit at BuildingEnergy NYCExhibitor FAQsInsurance RequirementBuildingEnergy 2015About BuildingEnergyVenueBuildingEnergy At A GlanceSchedule of EventsBuildingEnergy 15 SpeakersSpeaker ExportBuildingEnergy 15 SponsorsBuildingEnergy 15 ExhibitorsGet InvolvedPressPricingBuildingEnergy NYC 2014Schedule of EventsSpeakersBuildingEnergy NYC 14 SpeakersBuildingEnergy NYC 2014 SponsorsBuildingEnergy NYC 14 ExhibitorsPast Conference PresentationsBuildingEnergy Boston 2019 Keynote SessionBuildingEnergy Boston 2016 Video RecordingsPast Conference Slide PresentationsProgramsBuildingEnergy OnlineBuildingEnergy Bottom LinesAbout Bottom LinesJoin Bottom LinesMeet the FacilitatorsBuildingEnergy Pro ToursAbout Pro Tours2020 Pro Tour SeriesHost a Pro TourSponsor the Pro Tour SeriesView Past Pro ToursBuildingEnergy MagazineBuildingEnergy Case Study DatabaseSearch Case StudiesBuildingEnergy Masters SeriesMembershipLevels and BenefitsIndividualBusinessAcademicLifetimeJoin or RenewFind A MemberBusiness Member DirectoryIndividual Member DirectoryMember ResourcesAccount FAQsEvents CalendarCareer CenterBadgeNewsletterCommitteesMerch StoreNESEA/VSECU PartnershipInformation for IndividualsInformation for BusinessesSponsor Customer MembershipsCommunityBusiness Member DirectoryCommunity BlogEmerging ProfessionalsKate Goldstein FundThe Life & Legacy of Kate GoldsteinSupport the Kate Goldstein FundBE the FutureCurrent Scholarship OpportunitiesCareer CenterAwardsKate Goldstein Emerging Leader AwardDistinguished Service AwardProfessional Leadership AwardIn MemoriamEventsNESEA EventsCommunity EventsPast NESEA EventsDonateDonate NowMake a Pledge1% for the PlanetAboutHistoryGovernanceBoard of DirectorsBoard Meeting Schedule and MinutesBoard Member Job DescriptionBylaws and Governance PoliciesAudits & Tax ReturnsBoard CommitteesMember CommitteesStaffStrategic PlanAnnual ReportContactLoginMy AccountSearch
You are hereHome » Privacy Policy
Please Note: There have been scam emails circulating offering to sell a list of NESEA event attendees. This is a common scam targeting many events. The senders are in no way affiliated with NESEA and any lists they are claiming to offer are not NESEA attendee lists. We do not make our attendee lists available for resale.
NESEA Privacy Policy
Collection of Personal InformationNESEA collects and retains personal information that you provide to us, such as your name, postal address, phone number, email address, employer, and professional affiliations or credentials, along with transactional information when you participate in NESEA activities, including:
Joining or renewing as a NESEA member
Creating a nesea.org website account
Making a contribution to NESEA
Registering for a NESEA or BuildingEnergy event
Submitting a job posting, resume, case study, blog post, or conference session proposal
Creating a member profile or uploading a photo
Subscribing to NESEA communications
NESEA may also automatically collect technical information when you visit the nesea.org website, such as the IP address or operating system of your computer or phone. Sharing of Personal InformationNESEA maintains appropriate safeguards to secure the information we collect, and to ensure the appropriate use of information. NESEA does not share or disclose personal information to third parties, with certain, very limited exceptions. Attendee lists containing limited or no contact information for NESEA and BuildingEnergy events are provided to certain event sponsors, exhibitors, and hosts. When registering for an event, attendees are provided the opportunity to opt-out for that event. Payment TransactionsOnline transactions are conducted via an industry-standard secure encrypted channel.  Information is directly collected through a secure server by our credit card processor, and card numbers submitted online are not accessible to NESEA. Payment information is not retained by our processor once your transaction has been authorized and processed unless you have requested an automatic membership renewal or made a recurring donation. Opt-out and Communication  PreferencesYou may choose to not receive email communications by unsubscribing from all further email communications, or just communications of a specific type, by clicking the appropriate unsubscribe link at the bottom of a NESEA email message. You may also opt out of email or any other type of communication by sending a request to nesea@nesea.org, calling us at (413) 774-6051 ext. 19, or mailing a request to NESEA at 20 Federal St., Suite 8, Greenfield, MA 01301.
Control of Your InformationIf at any time you would like to update or request the deletion of your personal information in NESEA’s database, please use the contact information indicated above.
Member Contact MessagesThe nesea.org member contact message system is provided as a convenience for NESEA members. Messages are sent to the indicated recipient from the nesea.org website via regular Internet email and are not retained or monitored by NESEA staff. As is the case with regular Internet email, transmitted messages are not secure, so confidential information should not be included in contact messages. Members may opt out of this message system at any time by unchecking the contact option in their account profile or by requesting this using the contact information indicated above.
Website Visitor TrackingNESEA does not collect personal information in browser cookies, nor do we grant access to tracking information to third parties. We may use a service called Google Analytics to collect information about use of our  website. Google Analytics collects anonymous information such as how often people visit this site and what pages they visit. This data is only used internally by NESEA and is not shared with third parties. Links to Other WebsitesThe nesea.org website includes links to other websites.  We are not responsible for the policies and practices of other organizations, the contents of their websites, or how they use any information that you may provide to them. Policy ChangesNESEA may occasionally update this privacy policy, at which time we will post any changes on this web page. If significant changes are made, we will publish a notice that the policy has been modified and provide a link to the revised privacy policy.
Last updated 6/4/2018
Subscribe to NESEA communications!
©2020 Northeast Sustainable Energy Association - BuildingEnergy® is a registered trademark of Northeast Sustainable Energy Association
